https://www.directinvesting.com/privacy.cfm

Please login below, for login help click here
User or Subscriber ID:
Password:
Dividend Aristocrats
DRIP Plan Updates!
Submissions at Forbes.com
Getting Started
Former Moneypaper Subscribers, please click here for "one time only" access to each of the membership benefits
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy describes what information we collect, how we use that information in providing our products and services to you. When we refer to "Contact Information" we mean your name, address, telephone number, fax number and e-mail address.
Our Use of Information
We use your personal information in connection with delivering products and services to you. To do this, it may be necessary to share it with affiliates and other companies we work with. These include companies that manage and perform marketing services and companies whose products or services are provided as a benefit of your subscription. We may also share information with other third parties as permitted by law. For example, we disclose customer information in response to subpoenas, to agencies charged with protecting homeland security, and to help prevent fraud.
Sharing Our Information
We only share information under very limited circumstances - always under strict control against further disclosure. It is necessary to share such information, for example, with outside vendors who assist us in sending communications, shareholder reports and proxy materials to you, securities transfer agents who effect transactions in securities on your behalf. We require that these vendors keep your information confidential and we prohibit them from using your information for their own purposes.
In the event of a sale of assets, customer information may be one of the transferred assets.
Site Security.
We
take the security of information very seriously and has established security standards and procedures to prevent unauthorized access to customer information. We use industry standard means such as physical, electronic and procedural safeguards, including data encryption and secure socket layer technology. We update and test our technology regularly to maintain and improve the protection of our customers' information. We restrict access to personal information to employees and service providers for legitimate business purposes to assist in providing services to you. Employees who violate our privacy policy are subject to immediate dismissal and disciplinary action.
Click for Español
FOR MORE
INFORMATION
And a free copy of The Moneypaper's direct investing brochure, please enter your contact information below.
You will also be signed up to receive our monthly stock special.
You can unsubscribe at any time. We do not share your email with anyone.
First Name*
Last Name*
Address*
City*
State*
Select State
No State (N/A)
Alabama
Alaska
American Samoa
Arizona
Arkansas
Armed Forces AA
Armed Forces AE
Armed Forces AP
Manitoba
N.W.T.
New Brunswick
Newfoundland
Nova Scotia
Ontario
Prince Edward Island
Quebec
Saskatchewan
Yukon
Ethiopia
Falkland Islands (Islas Malvinas)
Faroe Islands
Fiji
Finland
France
French Polynesia
Gabon
Gambia, The
Gaza Strip
Heard Island and McDonald Islands
Holy See (Vatican City)
Honduras
Hong Kong
Howland Island
Hungary
Iceland
India
Indian Ocean
Indonesia
Taiwan
By email, you get the Monthly “Stock Special,” where the service fee for enrollment in a great DRIP stock is reduced.
E-Mail*
Confirm E-Mail*
Phone Number*
* Required Field.
PortfolioKeeper.com
|
mp63fund.com (DRIPX) |
About Us |
About Temper |
FAQs |
Help |
Privacy |
Site Map
The Moneypaper Publications LLC P.O. BOX 451, Rye, NY 10580
Phone: (800) 388-9993, (914) 925-0022 Fax: (914) 921-9318 9:00 a.m - 5:00 p.m EST
INVEST%® The Moneypaper® DirectInvesting® ©Copyright 2020 The Moneypaper Publications LLC All rights reserved
Enrolling in DRIPs: The Temper Enrollment Service is provided by Temper of the Times Investor Services, Inc., ("Temper") a registered broker dealer, member FINRA, SIPC. Temper does not make investment recommendations, nor does it make a market in any securities.
